Hello friends, today we are going to talk
about the recently launched Complete Health Insurance 2.0 of this company, so friends, earlier there used to be a
complete health insurance from IIT Loot,
but this month in November 2020, IIT Salman has
upgraded it and made it version 2.0,
so today we are going to discuss about this in detail
and I will
tell you about all the points
why the plan is better than before and
what new features have been set in it, so
friends, first of all let's talk about it, the company has
divided this new version into four points, in which the first plan
is our health, the second is taken help
sheet plus, the third line comes for health
and the fourth line comes relax plus, so
friends, these are categories of four new plans,
all of them have some new advances, so
what we will do is we will review it one by one,
today we will first
review tehsil and after that gradually
we will review all the four friends, all the four
videos which you will see on my channel  We will keep getting to see you, so
first of all let us
talk about everything, so the
benefits of this line, friends, first of all, is
that you can buy
any Jasmine worth Rs. 3 lakh to ₹5000000 and
suck in it, that is, after this, three
lakh, five lakh, seven lakh, ten lakh and in this way up
to 15, 2050, that you can take this much policy,
friends, if we
talk about this, then when you were not admitted in the hospital, then the
expenses before 30 days
and after that, when you have come home after recovery, then there are
expenses till the day with that, if we
talk about the room rent limit,
friends, here you get up to a single private air
conditioned room, in which there is no
amount of caffeine, you can go and get up to a single
private air conditioned room
in any hospital, see,
talk about treatment, friends, earlier there used to be
some specific positions here,
which used to be around one and a half hundred,
but now the company is offering it here  It has been
changed to All Day Care position, so now
you can get all the day care procedures done by any
doctor during pregnancy done in your day
care, then you will
get that facility here. Talking about no claim bonus,
friends, you will get ten percent
no claim bonus here. This year
also you have not taken any policy, so if you had taken a policy worth Rs
10 lakh and your
policy and no claim bonus was
Rs 1 lakh on it, then next year the
total policy of Rs 10 lakh plus Rs 1 lakh no claim bonus in your policy will be
Rs 11 lakh, because it keeps
increasing in this manner, it goes to a maximum of
fifty percent, that is,
after 5 years, if you have
not made any choice, then the policy of Rs 10 lakh will become Rs 15.
Talking about reset benefit, friends, this is a
very good unique point of this policy,
which you should understand well. That
reset benefit is that friends, if you have taken a
policy for the second time in a family and there are four children in a family.  There are
members, that is, if I talk about a general assembly,
here there are two sons and two children, then
what is there here is called recent
benefit that you can take it for unlimited times
or if the second one is over, then you
can again take 10 lakh 30 12, 10 lakh 34 thousand 500 grams, unlimitedly,
but here the condition is that you
cannot take it in the same way from within the same choice,
suppose if someone takes it for a heart attack
and the
bill comes for Rs 10 lakh
and in the same year he gets admitted to the heart attack again, then
you will not get that claim,
but if he gets admitted there due to some other problem, that is, due to
kidney problem, liver
problem, then he will get it
again, along with this,
if your family member,
suppose he has an email, he has
saved Rs 10 lakh in the family, if his message is
needed through Jhala, then he will get it
if his  One child
needs another and that too will be available in a year.
If other children also
need Rs 10 lakh in a year, then
that too will be available here friends, that means you
can also see it in this way that
a special benefit of Rs 10 lakh
is available here for everyone. Okay friends, so let's move ahead,
today we will talk about treatment here,
like Ayurveda, Siddha,
Unani, if any
treatment is given to you in the hospital
and that is a rule from the government, then you
get its facility here also.
Moving ahead friends, let's talk about ambulance cover,
that too is a very good
feature of theirs, that here you are given it after leaving one percent of the time.
If suppose here
you have taken five lucky policies,
a famous ₹5000 in the policy of Tapasya, then
what will you get in it that
you can take cover of one ambulance up to ₹5000 on every horse show,
whereas if you look at other policies, the
maximum would have been ₹1500, 2009.  The
maximum here is 10,000, meaning
if you have a pass of 10 lakhs, then you can claim
even more for 10,000 from the company for hospitalization.
If we talk about entries,
friends, then any healthy person from 18 years can take it here
and there is no
limit. Here, if you are 65 years old,
70 years old, 75 years old, if you have a
medical kit, then you can take this policy. If we
talk about dependent child or
new born baby cover, then if any
new born baby is born in your family, then
you
can add him/her under this policy under night dress
or if you have any dependent child, then there is a cover for him/her.
Here, till the age of 21,
you can keep your child under this policy.
Friends, the best
thing about ICC that I find in it is the airplane
service guarantee. These people write to you on your browser
that our film
service guarantee is that within four hours, you will get
your address, your settlement and other  Limbo
Cement will settle the claim
within four days, if we are not able to do this then we
will charge you a penalty, so till now, as far as I have
seen in the entire industry, there is
no ATM service guarantee anywhere, so they make a commission
that the claim gets processed in 30 minutes, 1 hour, 2
hours, 90% of our claims get resolved
in this much time but they do
not use the word guarantee and
talking about celebration discount, friends, if
you buy a 2-year policy here, then
you will get a
10 percent discount on the second year premium, similarly
if you select 30 here, then you will
get a 15 percent discount on the third year premium,
friends, health checkup is
available to you every year, under health checkup,
you have some listed checkups
which you can get done by going to the diagnostic center
or you can call the
members of the diagnosis center and call them to your
home, they will do the checkup at your home itself, so in
every policy, you have
two coupons for yourself.  It is for two adults
and they can redeem it every year.
If we talk about balance points, friends, then
balance points are available here.
Suppose you participate in a marathon
or any test, you have participated in swimming
or you have
joined a gym, if you share its bill or its
proof here, then
you get points here according to every category
and the value of that point is
25 paise and you can redeem that point
in OPD benefit.
This money is signed in your policy
and you can go to OPD and avail its benefit.
This kind of problem reimbursement mode is on. Let's
talk further,
friends, this cover for expenses was
not available earlier, that if
you have to take something or an organ from someone, then the
companies will offer its express cover and they will do this
now including the facility and talk about Dominic Strauss
performance. Friends, don't slice the
ingredients. Pushpendra Singh says that if you
take the patient for this  He is not in a position to get
admitted in the hospital
or in
all the hospitals near you, there is
no bed available there, then in this condition,
you are provided with doms and aspiration,
all the facilities are provided at your home itself, just
like a hospital, so that
facility is available here,
friends, let's talk about ambulance cover, which was not there earlier, in
such a situation, it has been added here
and this is your Sudha Sum Insured, that is,
suppose you have taken a policy of ₹ 1000000,
then here you will also get this ambulance cover,
that too of Rs 1000000, so
friends, what the company is saying is that this cover is not give, that
means there is no shortage, if
suppose you used the cover of balance of ₹ 2000 ₹ 3000, then
if you have taken a policy of your total 10 lakhs, then it will
not be deducted from it, it is over and above,
leave your impatience and go ahead and do it right here.  Time is fine and ₹10
here you get this ambulance cover,
all this editor time is left, friends there
is also a protector on top, inside this it means
no claim bonus, they have to
change their definition language a little, so
here if any of your creams which do
not go above fifty thousand in a year, then what will happen, the
company will make a claim and you will
not be given no claim bonus next year, but
this pen has an inbuilt feature inside it, for this
you do not have to pay extra money,
in it, suppose your pen is
below 50 thousand, then you will get this
ten percent no claim bonus, that
is fine and with this, those
policies will increase a little, if we
talk about tele consultation, friends, then this
seems to be their best unique feature also
because in today's time of convention
or considering the convenience of the people, in the
meantime, people do
not want to visit the ashram doctor or the hospital, here
they have provided a bag cancer question of the doctor which is 24 * 7 i.e.  It
is available for you here the entire day. You should have a higher tech care,
so you download that app and in it there is
an option of doctor at Delhi Cantt station. If you click on it, then
you will get a college of doctors
who have MBA certificate. You
can tell them about your problems and they will send
you its prescription on email, asking
you to take these medicines or you can do it better. So
friends, this device is available to you on video chat option,
which is a
cost-free feature in your policy. Friends, here the
facility of dietician nutrition consultation is also available. If you want
us to take a consultation, in this you
want to maintain your diet or you
want to take dietary supplements, then you
can consult a doctor there, that too is
free of cost. Friends, one good thing and
I got lucky is the ambulance assistance
which has been added to Universe, that if
their ambulance and system service is available in your city, you
can check it by going to their website, there  What will happen is that if you
call Amritsar station, the
automatic doctor there
will assess you whether you really
need emergency ambulance service right now. If that is the case and the
facility is available within your city, then you will be provided with
that ambulance service provider on a cashless basis.
You do
n't need to make any payment there. Generally,
you pay for the ambulance service
and after that, it gets credited
to your account. But here the company has provided an
ambulance, if you go to their account
and click there, then the
important ambulance assistant will come to your home
and that too on a questionable basis.
Open the settings. Friends, if
any of your family members gets a critical
illness like cancer or
you are on dialysis, then it prevents you from doing this. There are many
big
medical institutions like brain tumor. If such a
situation arises and you want to
get your opinion from a doctor,
open the settings and say whether we should get this
treatment or surgery done.  If you do
n't want it, then that subsidy
is also available in it, so you
can take advantage of this as well. The company will
not charge you any extra for this. So, the
covers that I am telling you about right now are all invested in this plan, for this the
company will
not charge you any extra. But there are
some advances that I am telling you about,
for this the company will charge you some extra
money and this service will also be
added to it and to your policy. First let's
talk about Someshwar tractor.
Friends, the semiconductor here
says that whatever sum you have insured from me, so
friends, what happens from
time to time, you are also seeing
that inflation keeps increasing. If today
I take a policy of Rs 5 lakh, then
after the next five years it will not be sufficient. So, the
inflation and hospital expenses are
increasing day by day. So, keeping this in mind, the
company has added
a new addition in it. Understand the protractor.
What is there in it? This is our government
organization, it is called Central
Statistical Organization, it issues a report every year.
Consumer Price Index determines that
it will affect your profit on this thing. Now, here I am
saying that the companies have
fixed a margin of six percent on this. So,
suppose you have taken a policy of Rs. 10 lakh, then
its margin is six percent,
that is Rs. 7000. If you have
taken five policies, then it is clear from this that
Rs. 3000 will be added to your insurance cover every year, that is,
if the policy is of Rs. 500 in the first year, then it will be of Rs.
5 lakh 30 thousand in the next year, then the insurance cover will be
of Rs. 7000, it will keep increasing gradually in an easy manner.
Your no claim bonus is a different
thing, that will also keep increasing and this
too will increase in a different way, your
no claim bonus will increase. So friends, such a
situation also comes with us that
suppose you have all your regular claims
and in this situation the company never
increases your base claim. If
you have taken such a product, then
what can you do, your base claim will
also increase gradually.  If it keeps increasing then I would
say that this is a good thing, you should
definitely think about it,
friends let's talk about the train product,
camp road, friends there are many
such requirements which IRDA has
declared as not visible in its,
friends what does not visible mean, friends like club
money, admission charges, etc. which
earlier the insurance companies did not provide, that is,
if I talk about a bill of 1 lakh, then the
tortoise had to pay ₹3000
from his pocket, but
today it has reduced a lot and
if you have a big area, then also in that,
if you have taken this protector, then
you do not need to pay even ₹1 in the hospital, the entire
percentage of your claim will be
settled by the company,
whatever money you had to pay initially for
TCS or anything, we will
not do it all, but here friends there is a
cover here which is not available in the market right now, it is
easily available in 12 companies
but there are more conditions in it, but here
But to be a little clear, the condition of
worldwide cover has been kept in it, friends,
if your plan is above 10
lakhs, then you can
take worldwide cover here in two years
and in Canada, you
can get your treatment done anywhere in the world, but the condition in this is
that your travel relation should be for
45 days or not,
if suppose you have gone on 1st January, then
you can stay here till 15th February, then
whatever expenses will be incurred in this, the company will
offer you that on cashless basis, if
you have got entry here, then you had to get it done
and you were told that the
treatment is better in that specific country
and I should do it that way,
and if you have another one, then you can get it done there, for the
shoulders which you have here
and depression, then you
can use it twice a year, total
care will be provided, you will get a necklace,
but here a condition is that
whatever bill is made,
you will have to share 10 percent of it from your pocket.  It means
if suppose the bill of Dussehra is made then you have to pay Rs.
9 lakhs from here and around Rs.
1 lakh from the company from your pocket and
friends this is another deficiency, if suppose
you have taken worldwide cover for Dussehra policy then it is worth Rs. 20
lakhs, Rs. 10 lakhs for your
treatment in India and
Rs. 1000000 for your treatment worldwide,
friends one good point is the Super No
Claim Bonus, Super No Claim Bonus says
that I told you earlier that
quality content organizations get Bigg Boss
which goes up to a maximum of 50%, if
you add this bonus and add it inside it then the
no claim bonus that you were getting,
you will get 50% more here i.e.
50% if you have a policy of up to ₹5 lakhs then
that 50% will go up to a maximum of 10 lakhs,
if we give an example here
that you have a Dussehra policy then a
policy of Rs. 10 lakhs will be applicable to you next year  The trap will be that
if you do not take any claim and
next year again it will become Rs 2000000
if we do not take any claim, okay and
we were getting 10 percent extra from the back here, so
our 20 percent that is also added,
but if your policy is
between Rs 15 lakh to Rs 50 lakh, then
you will get 50% no claim bonus,
not even 100 percent, but 200 percent, for
example, if we understand that I have 20 lakhs, then 50
percent of the 20 lakh policy is 10 lakh, this will be
positive in the next year, but that will come third,
then I did not take 40, then I did not take
less, by bringing 50, then I did
not take any claim, then Rs 60 lakh will be confirmed for that
and if we go back here, we have taken
4-4, if we did not take any claim, then 40 percent
that one, okay, so see here how much
no claim bonus will be added on, as if the
premium of your policy was to go only that
which is going, so this one here  The
thing that is very useful is
friends, if you talk about Hospital Delhi Catch, then ₹5, if you
take it, then the minimum is three
days, you should have notification of performance and maximum
pain between three days to
10 days, that is, within about 7 days,
your selection etc., and you will
get the money for seven days within it, so if I talk about 5 lakh
airplane, then you will get ₹1000 per day,
this snake, and if you have a plan up to 10 lakh, then
you will
get ₹2000 per day, if you have a plan of 15 lakh to 50,000,
then you will get ₹3000, if
you have added any of these, then
you will get its additional benefit,
friends, and there are some additional benefits,
I will also tell you about that, one is the
Condolence Benefit, it is fitted in
that wherever your hospitalization goes beyond 10 days, it goes
extra and
you have taken this benefit.  So this company will give you a
lump sum of ₹2000. The feature of nursing home is that
friends, wherever the doctor says
that you can get your treatment at home,
you are going after getting discharged from the hospital,
we also call this post graduation, then
after that
you may need nursing at home, okay,
if any qualified nurse comes to your house
and provides you service, then
here you have this Dongri, then
₹3000 birthday, we will keep
giving you reimbursement for that nurse and the
maximum coverage will be of 15 days,
compensation and visit friends, this is such a
situation that suppose you
live in some other city and your family is
in another or it can also happen that you go to
some other city for work
and there you fall ill
or an accident happens and you get
admitted in the hospital of the same city, then at any time
if your hospital stay is more than 15 days in this situation, then
your family
members  The immediate family members, like
children, parents, if you
want to call them from your home to that city, then
whatever 19 years and then there will be
economic class, it will be and investment will be done,
its limit is maximum
of 20000 rupees, so if you want to add this also in it, then you
can do it, if we
talk about Pretty Glass, friends, the company has
made a list of glasses because
I will give you the details in the description or
you will get the details inside Roshan
and from that, if you get any critical illness, then
you can use a specific cover like
40000, 5 nights, 10 lakhs, whatever
my new policy is,
except for the time the news is here, then that
money will be deposited in your account,
suppose you have
taken a critical illness cover of five amounts, positive 5 lakhs,
for which you will have to pay additional money, if
you get any of these diseases, then
you will get treatment of 5 lakh rupees
because you have health insurance along with
this  According to the benefit, a
benefit i.e. ₹5 will also be credited to your bank account
for which you can deposit it in your account.  You can
use it for expenses in the family members,
you can use it for your children's education
or you
can also use it for your treatment and
while talking about dental cover, friends, there is a
waiting period in critical illness which will be app locked when
you have taken the policy, its cover will
start after TDS, after this you have to keep in mind
that if we talk about personal accident,
friends, it is available only in diet
and medical benefit,
you will not get these things in matches, so whatever
cover you have taken here, 5 lakh or
toxic, for example, if
someone dies in an accident and gets injured, then
that money and limited normally goes
to the member and if you have permanent
disability, friends, that is, like
loss of lips, cutting of hands, going to the
house of a loved one, then there is
permanent total displacement for this tuition, so in that, the
company provides you the entire money, in this,
friends, let us talk about the application here, that
What are some negative points of the question that the company has,
so friends, there are some problems in every plan
and almost the
same thing is here too, so the two years waiting period
is clear, whatever you have deleted from PM West Indies,
like suppose you
said that I had a hernia problem, or
I had a sinus problem, or
fiber, or I had hypertension, then
you can put any such picture of yours in the heading
and put a 2-year
waiting period in it and only after 2 years that
problem of yours will be covered, the
second waiting period is friends here, like
cataract, knee joint replacement,
strong sinus, these friends are such
problems which are ignored not at one time but for a long time,
and in all the companies,
you will get a 2-year waiting period for this, in the
first 30 days you will
not get any cover here, you will only get accidental
cover, the company has added a cover of 2015 equivalent,
which works only within 15 days,
okay, that is wrong, I will also tell you  Let me tell you
what that cover is. Okay, so after 30 days
you understand that this policy
will be activated normally except in case of accident like
cataract. Friends, there is a limit here that you will
get insurance on 20 thousand rupees. If your
plan is ₹5, which is
required after every year for cataract and ₹1000, but
you will get it if your plan is
above 5 lakhs. So friends,
keeping in mind the crowd, the company has
added some special benefits
in its policy which are free of cost.
For this, only some company will add an addition of the child for
its consultation. As I
told you, when you can consult a doctor,
okay,
you can also take consultation from this point within the case of comment,
but this, which used to be like this earlier for 30 days, has become
of Edifice here.
No Clear Scanner No Claim Bonus, which has been
deleted and returned to the home. If you do not
have it, don't have it, okay, even then it does
not make any difference.  Ultimately, the
company has said that if you
take any of them till now, you will get Rs 1 lakh. There
is justice in this, the claim of wind will
not be credited to your account.
Sameer videos will happen, but the bonus that you were supposed to get, you have
taken 20% of 10%, 50%, then you will get that here.
Okay, Som Health Care too, friends,
we have added here, it provides maximum
service, that your doctor says
that you too have got it and you
need to be treated, but you do not say that
why am I not getting it in the hospital,
okay, I do
not want to go to the hospital because the infection can
spread even more there, so there are
many such companies in the market
which provide home care service,
here your entire setup is installed at home itself, so
here
from both cashless and investment point of view, that
service is available here, you can email it,
its service is
free of cost till 31 March 2019.  After 31 March 2019, the
company will decide whether to
extend the service or not
because they will have to take ID approval, if it is
extended then I will intimate you, so
friends, I have told you completely about this plan,
in the upcoming videos I will
also review the remaining three plans, so I
hope friends,
you have understood this plan and if
you still have any questions, you can ask me,
my WhatsApp number is displayed on every screen and you can
see it, you can
ask me in the comment section, you will find
my email ID in the description,
you can also see it there, so
friends, I hope you liked this free service,
if you liked it then do
not forget to share it with your friends, do
like the video, I will meet you friends
in the next video, thank you very much for watching this video.